Durai.
During. War.
During
a war
during or.
During. World
War two. A.
To. War.
Or.
A honor or war
when. It is.
A whole world will
reward.
Drive. A.
Car and it can make God more
a. Nice guy my wife and I can go to
morrow morning with my carry on not want
to have
a nightmare sensation right
steady Barbara. Thank
you. Rob.
I don't need
a job I don't know. Where I
can describe or nobody but I
happen to have
a photograph. CARTER So you
combine business with pleasure little
Judge Doolittle is about this is about
getting married on his dime without his
consent or his daughters what you could do
in the chief topic of conversation about
these budget. Office talk Carter isn't
a word of truth I'm judged
a little and I think so is
that so he doesn't like it he.
Good morning just do
a lot of. Well
it seems that everybody around here found
out that I was. When I was up in Boston
what are you doing in Boston.
Remember you sent me up there to get
a deposition on the case to get it that's
all this was always horseplay while I was
in Boston after I got the deposition I
had a few hours to spare so I. Just
a few I heard I was gone on I
got married. I got married.
And I guess I got married and my other.
Position. They are so.
Much there.
That's just sort of
a lighter. Matter. And I gin this will be
a surprise to some people. No
sir Well I don't know it all happened rather
suddenly. We met on Boston Common and
I arrived. And then I took
a little stroll around the common.
I saw are standing there. Just
standing there. And Senator Warner. Who's.
Mrs Mason My wife. She was
my wife she's my wife
now. And I got the sender out
of her eye and humanity.
The moment we looked at the. Moment we
looked at each other and then yes or.
In this country Congratulations
mention. Like you very much.
Like your opinion on this or oh this
is you Mr Mason special messenger.
What is it. What is it. A letter from my
wife. What you do have in
Boston. Right here in town.
In town and she read your letter.
She likes to write letters. Sort of
a little custom we have she wrote me
a letter the first day she met me right
as soon as she got home and she's written
a one ever sent even coming down on the
train together she wrote me once I got
a letter from our it's sort
of like I sort of say.
Judge. Two people get
married they usually go on
a honeymoon I didn't I
don't approve. Of time.
And I thought about Higgins against. The
only one of the on his nose in this case
John the kind of the next
week well if I could get
a continuance opposing counsel would
consent but I talked to Mr Harper all this
morning and he agreed to
a continuance Wow All right. Well
Judge I'm afraid we wouldn't be able to
make it in a week. We couldn't make it on
a wait but my wife and
I had sort of planned
a trip to Europe on the
Normandy. Take two weeks then.
And after I got sent out to James I we
talked for a little while and then we. Took
a little walk around the Commons. And
how you walk for quite
some time I went over. For
a bite. And had
a bite. There is
a god an unconventional meeting that
these cookies are delicious they're made
sour cream I'm crazy about sour cream I'm
crazy about Jay. Johnson
The Young and imposes
on our mother this is just Are you
visiting relatives here in New York idea.
Well yes and no not exactly I
came over with Jolly from Boston
together last night well yes mother
we thought as long as we were
engaged. I know I'll bet you must
be Mrs nice you know so little
about me it all happened so
suddenly I should think it Russ.
What did your family have to say
about it I have no family oh didn't
jump say something about your taking
a course in genders Yes but I gave
it up after I met Johnny I'm sort of
a post-graduate course. If you have
a talent for writing take my advice and
develop it was your young one needs all run
time and energy for a career
if you think marriage is
a career in itself only Indeed emphatically
That's why one mustn't rush into it
pell mell marriage is
a business and it is serious business
partnership in this brick distance of the
work when this prepare for it
and so many things to. Well
Dana learn all those after we're married
I hope and pray that that day will not
come from many years mother what
do you mean You mean we shouldn't
insect ical enough there's no
reason for Jane to develop into
a little house so DRUDGE Well I hope you
understand I have nothing against Jay In
fact I like I like
a vet him. Well I'm glad
to do mother because you
remember
a little while ago you asked whether she'd
come to New York to visit relatives well
as a matter of fact she has
come to the yard there's
a she's visiting some
right now you see or when
there is
a. Call
mother everybody gets margin or
a lighter just because there is also one
of them looked like while I was small I
saw her. That's then down
you have children of your own I suppose
you love them and will turn nice to them
and they'll go up and leave you and you
think yes and. That's the way. You said you
know that this mother Don't
excite yourself. I'm all right.
I wish or is it possible happiness.
I think perhaps because.
I've found
a place to live of course some place to
live well of course not mother you'll stay
with us. We're going to find
a new apartment we've talked is all over
and Jane Lynch says want to go we couldn't
think of anything else where we see.
Polls of bill right. Or returning
maybe we shouldn't of gotten married.
Moving shouldn't got murder or.
Hospital shopping. As physical as
a shopping. Don't get into too many
strawberries I long to get rashes and don't
forget to make
a med he's been coaching lamington haven't
he had pneumonia last fall about was
twelve years ago I feel fine now people
can just combines most. At risk.
By going on
a mother or two only to
break. The ice. Process
keeping tabs he's got to protect.
What I think of because he don't want to
have left out the window but I suppose
a look at the size of this is so intimate.
What is it but that's nothing nor is it
something that is not
the capacity to reach
the yes. I said it's
a going away present time to me
job you Shadi the value the.
Journey. You live I couldn't
live in the office.
Today. You know when I was in school I was
brought to two things going out to both
employees at the same time we're.
Going to get the stuff you get this is a
bigger the struggling you couldn't get
a bigger bed in the Oh I think it's
beginning to work is one for the ideas.
Like oh sure OK. Johnny This is the first
time out I said I've been away from
America to. Meet just
a few. Because. Jane. Your
mom and I send you into gotta go I'll.
Never see you know it's true that away I
should. Be sure to get that put it in the
lockers and. I hadn't been for the cinema
and would never. Want to meet.
A man much sooner than
he hasn't just been you.
Perfectly you know just amazing. Where
it's a level. To be
a miss. Well
hello Carter and I'm
going to come down just
a little Send me. A
card that says. This is
my wife. In the office how do you have
another good thing I got her in time you've
got just about ten minutes and there's
a way to get off the boat to get off what
you're talking about begins again pagans
What about. Going to games they're going
to go on the calendar the next week i'll
what that's for your most I can I got
a continuum from home one you think you
did well my dad why do you ask Harbaugh
about
a game is what about or you know along the.
Way they can do this to you oh I can do
this what do you think the
public one of the I think I am
a potter so I don't even have
a party can put you out anyway you know
what you're all over the place is that what
you want me to tell do a little yes oh
a car. Are you sure that his case going on
this way Monday morning at nine o'clock
. Excuse
a system Jane I'm glad you said that you
know yeah sure look this he can first take
it's pretty important showcase the most
important case in the world this is
important of course but just not to
get lipstick on him I hope you know
a lawyer sort of like
a doctor so what you're going to disregard
your own convenience. Of this you can
only go on the list and believe me I tell
do little to jump in the lake and I'd be
going to the risk of losing my
job but if I win the case I get
a chance to go in with
a firm and A. Firm like this but
it's my honeymoon
a little knowledge of my
honey. Sir just some things
a man just can't do. Some things
a man just can't do.
Thanks
that's Carter thought it was
funny last night take that live
a pill never try apologizing like this
they get my take that judge do nothing.
Someone would step on that is singing. We
still have the tickets my hope you can
be taken
thanks
to your pool
thank
.
God. The alligator Peden it took.
Your mother in law already when you want
to play God I'm going to marry that right
there with the yeah the good the so wrong
to fix my hair I didn't get the buy. The
property where you should have made
an edit up what went. Wrong sure I
thought I could just do it alone my right
of course met with the car I thought I'd
have to have it on the left you seem to
think I've never done this oh no no there's
no whatever you want to wind up
a down the road ahead in the left side
with the right side where I worked before
the right side with the water glass then.
How do you think the table works is
a little crowded that guy
would drive me crazy. And
I think the job and us do it for.
There was nothing in it back and
that's a good. Would you be a D.N.C.
Event he has the appetizer
sixty five course idea.
I think you have too many on the place and
shouldn't there be gun issues as well as
this is
a trade when I gave I don't know how many
hands expect you to have around this
place it's just so much
a body can do I'm only human I fix the
canopy for humanity as you seem to have so
much to do
a little bit too much to get in the sand
addressing honestly and I know my human
only opportunities are going to benefit
others and the single too long to learn
that. I really know what's right
now you can stand just so much and I'm only
human but you can't do that oh I can't
please everybody Oh but I mean
my guess would be here in
a minute. Well
I'll see you through the night but I will
even at nine o'clock chop in order to
protect them I'm thirty three go back to
Cairo and nobody is going to stop me I'm
only human and watch the
potatoes in it. Didn't
And I have so much to do with the extra
gas and everything don't you think we've
got
a new word tonight and sort of leave her alone
but you asked me to see about the canopy
Well I know but it's
a great deal for one person to do and too
many of us telling her what to do only
upsets her that I didn't try
to help. With this journey.
I think you forgot the one. Or grandpa's
favorite up call up the little club called
up for a nice night as Burgundy
on the barge here how about
a chum of course will be very
much like most hurry up and grab.
However gone everything's lovely an ultimatum
for madness of final She's moving on
tonight so I feel seriously gonna blow. Up
why have more problems girls always got
up there was like a safe
place where you just allowed
a joint for peace like what would you do
with the what you said I didn't have that
look on the search out back of the I
was always the ones behind. That was
a brilliant idea of your god can you just
do that at the last minute judges are
like corn beef and cabbage they're always
together and that impossible to Epcot I
thought you had to ask him to come you
know send some sort of update carders or
what could I do. Not only do all the
guys work for the freedom or we're.
All going to be different my name goes
up there on that door Johnny you really
think so for a spark to get there and
I'll put on a beef roast beef do
a little delight you know I don't have any
make your to put in but you never get it
it's all right tween roast beef and Pagans
against pagan how can we lose so is
going to the I'm
a mother and the daughter do little
things Mrs Smith do little such
a Mason Oh Johnny. Then I when my
motives were no trial begins again
second I had
a minimal do little but I did what did
he say he said he couldn't handle Barram
self when he's from your table tonight
he'll eat out of my hand and while I tell
the car i will we have Sonoma do we go place
our way to do things that I don't like
that time whether I want to MacWorld you
know they did your name has to be less
well for the time being anyway
you know what it means to
a man who doesn't know from like that
you know what it means to finally get
a man like you in it yeah
yeah. Scrutinize necking.
Nice Eunice didn't know what I know but you
know student was not never you know she
had one how do you know what time of year
to get dressed well you know when I asked
him what come up. Grab up will
be here any minute Good evening
Wow Good evening we were getting ready I
have great news why should I judge we're
having
a row to be we're almost
before dinner. When
you campus I'm all right and just do a
little I said well Why yes thank you and
a similar line for Judge
too little now you have
a mom. And
a salad folks are judged too
little I put on they are
the funniest thing happened the other day
just to little I ran across the yearbook
of my husband's class in college and the
class prophecy was picked as the one most
likely to succeed was that the other day I
ran across the yearbook and by husbands
class in college and
in the class prophecy.
Higgins again take it as
a pretty important case isn't it where
we like to think all of our cases are
important
a little kind of today maybe the big client
of tomorrow or your soul right judge
for instance we got
a client the other day that. Oh
dear. What happened here I scream at me I
told you to get that I thought they fixed
.
Get this notice me. Is it true just do
a little something you got up in the
furnace What makes you think I'd excuse my
place oh yes we're going to have
a blood transfusion I want to speak about
if I think we have got what I mean is
that we're getting some new
blood into the binding
a junior partner Oh just
answer the call because no
one is seven dollars
a month in Iraq my twelve dollars
Not right now get it for you.
Maybe that's the way we keep an Old Firm
young. I've been doing this excuse me for
a hug every five years but it's quite a
job to pick the right man I think it's
a question of. As
a rule I cast my own judgment when it comes
to thinking man screws me place I just
I think there's nothing like
a woman's intuition all your soul right
judge of course Eunice doesn't know much
about law but she's traveled all over the
world and she does know people. Five
years ago it was at her suggestion that I
took was to identify with God so well I
beg your pardon. This year I have
again consulted my daughter and now
a new name moves up on the door Allardyce
beginning next Monday the name of the sun
will be do a little message might do
a little. And cause
a current of that graduation
that's wonderful isn't it
and I always knew you had
a new car. Well I'd like to propose
a toast to the new partner on
it but we seem to have run.
Out of. This many more why.
May I have to know people
number please certainly.
If you like
a stamp Thank you. Could have taken please
surely Thank you.
And I tell you gentlemen of the joy that
the fans of Hagan's whether I'm brotherly
than a man motivated solely by
a does I or maliciously and hatefully to
interfere with their brothers rights and
privileges deliberately and improperly
departed the waters of the straight one
gentleman I leave the determination of
these matters in your hands confident that
your verdict will bring justice to my
client the plaintiff in this action.
Gentlemen of the jury you are now
retired to arrive at the verdict.
Change how long you been here I got here
just as you started your summation John it
is wonderful you should have been here
when I cross-examined Hagan's you are now
the other one you skin the
lives torn apart really come.
Second was the first birth mark.
Congratulations to my smart
work you get us while job.
Hold. On everything without
a Great Britain one is
that out is this my.
Boy.
Now is all yours was amazed me
on my. First and then again
sometimes I swear much I was I mean. That.
I wanted to go in all of the perfect.
Heat my mother when I got back. On my.
Journey. You know lacking
a sauna don't you think you just beautiful.
Don't you think he's just beautiful.
Jane don't you think you look so old oh
well what do you know what I mean don't you
think it was about six months old or
a year old Don't be silly darling Can't
you think you just beautiful. Big rose up
look like you how can he has all your
features I don't see how you can tell that I
looked when just
a quick those around his eyes are just
like yours when you're happy. He doesn't
look happy just looks it's kind of boring
Well you'd be bored too if you've been
through what he has. Done to
you think you just. Change it
I grabbed. Don't you think you just.
Messed around the feel of your first
that the show you so keep it from me it
prevents create OK yes I know mother is
a Johnny doesn't watch out still
doesn't just point look at the show.
Drink can I do soft drink play. What
you've done I own was knocked in will you
please move over your. Neck me
show you how I know how mother they showed
me in the hospital now you don't rather
guy just I ain't patting him.
He looks good maybe the World Cup's too hot
no it wasn't Mother I tested it it was
just right was it he wanted to
talk to John John to me sure sure
sure. No not that one this one
Paul I look at that chanced.
Marchin can I help if you did my D.M.
Will Johnny you better go in the
kitchen and warm his milk now.
I have. No down. Oh Hello
Lou yeah he's saved. That's the comic
strip is not that he's just hungry I thought
of my dad to fetch the comic he kind
of finally. Found
a rare good. Hard
Mr Harry already that.
They don't keep your hands
you don't. Have to say.
I got.
Used to you mother you would just turn three
if you could see down time he wouldn't
cry soon as we're organized I don't think
he has to be said on the bottle I haven't
had the baby complain if you don't have
a small bottle for six months so I won't
say anything I won't say anything
that's not my idea What do you think of the
present the more gratifying for this is
someone going to buy
a book. Deposit than dollars. That's
a lot of money for the little
guy who doesn't plunge just
a little into bankruptcy after that hospital
bill is got more cash on the back and
I and I think it's very considerate of
Judge Doolittle to think about the baby's
future you know this is the future that
worries me it's the present what are we
going to put him for why God is in our
room you know he kept you awake all last
night and I do take into consideration
before you're going to disappear in time now
why should it's not my own room and so small
Oh no dear I wouldn't think of it well
look don't know why can't we keep him in
our room in the daytime in the living room
at night too far away from the bedroom I
have on the banning too near the kitchen
but I guess I'll have to do could I see you
for I mean it's please what is it Hilda
young mother didn't know Heidi venue was
a vague because she didn't tell me US of A
You mean you don't approve of my having
a baby oh yeah that's your business you can
have as many new babies as sure that I
thank you they get it but my business is
cooking you can get somebody else to rush
the diapers.
Sean and I just don't worry about
us or wish I could go back
to the hospital after this leaches up I'm
going to get your house in the country
you're going to have a room all
by yourself you're going to have
a garden where you can ride
around in your bicycle and I'm
a mother mother coming Jane
walk she's smiling at me.
While I guess. That's guess.
Home Whoa whoa whoa whoa.
Whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
whoa whoa whoa home.
And you know that I'm going.
Well everyone's. Going to Lose same
old crowd in years old was spoken
well at O'Malley make quite
a speech. I. Want to sit
on the Stock Exchange
so Campbell you just came back from
opening the London office. Did you make
a speech. Or did you say. On
the you know just kind of
sweet talk about reviews will be much.
Less big but the short.
One and I have to say
in most likely to succeed you still I'm
glad that your speech was where you
want to move or we could be talking
about money don't you don't need.
The cycle. All I could think of is my
achievement what I've accomplished how far
I've gone. I suppose I could have told
them that I used your money all of it life
or nature for the support for the
your money my money but didn't as
a make was very much you know maybe I
could have told him that the baby had to
sleep in the dining room or whatever
that's only temporary so we got another
possible because I can't afford to get you
a decent job and I'll say
those things. So managing I
can't see straight. Thing is to minimize
it all. I don't want you to do any
disagree to see what you. Need to know
what's wrong come on honey I'll get you some
of the. Ballots
she should I'm going to have
a cold chicken stand right in the face
which. Darling The trouble with you is you
let people step on you have
a look down that office. More about law
the car level though the expect people to
recognize you then you want to run dry
once you recognize it yourself could get
along without you for
a minute and you know everybody else knows
her better but she does too only takes
advantage of you I told you when he
promoted Cotterell your head you should
a quick ride out of. The park by I know
your mother and me I wish you'd forget
about us well if I lost my job she'll want
me they wouldn't let you go you have far
too valuable if you left to little quiet
hands and knees and beg you to come back
and in
a zone Oh you don't know do not know but I
know you all you have to do is speak up
that's got to do
a little don't ask for your
rights demand the value I
want to budge without running in Boston
promise you I guess you are but I want to
later well I don't want to but I will
later. Just like the platinum dime so
that Kuwait. Was the
main cloak and way to.
About four hundred yard I can afford
to buy what are you a man or a mouse
a mouse. Jabe's you know what's the matter
with you you're too modest you don't
appreciate yourself though I do want the
platinum ring I want to for Coke not to
make one but
a fur coat and I want to honeymoon on the
Normandy and I want to apartment big
enough the arm of the baby so the baby
won't have to sleep in the dining room to
get that from you get everything I want
everything that's coming to me but first
you've got to get what's coming to you.
Just knew how to go up Bob He is like it's
easy to just walk right into the office
you've got it Jerry and you you don't want
him to do a little job as
a Sam's for you this time you're going to
work you go right up to him and you say
just do
a little there's something I've got to say
to you right now so you can talk to him
like that have you ever tried. Now
a genuine you don't understand I have our
guard down there like that and he'd say
What is it Mason say you never notices
around this life well then stand but don't
let him interrupt you speak in peace and
so on no I don't think you put it as easy
to do here on the ketch you get down Thomas
downtown or uptown what difference does
it make you not ask you know favoring
your demand here I want to listen. To you
Millicent thought OK All right well what
I say you're just too little I've been
working for you for five years I've given
you everything that should be every ounce
All right what I say no doubt about it
never questioned your ability or your
loyalty and I said just
a little what are you going to do about
it I think what you'll say Mason what you
expect me to do just do little the right
thing why I'm running and I want to be
taken into the firm and
you say you say plenty O.
Matter what you say you'll see
Judge to settle I think in
a race that you new partnership
around. Or else you can accept my
resignation. For committee
All right. One hundred one
do that some of these days
some of these days tomorrow tomorrow
tomorrow morning at ten o'clock. Well if you
think I should have thought darling there's
no time like the present well c'mon now
let's start with the beginning I think I
walk into the office and I say just do
a little bit something I have to say to
you right now Judge do it all there's
something I've got to say to you
right now either I got a raise and
a junior partnership
either I got a raise and
a junior partnership or you think that
my resignation or you can accept my
resignation of effect of I mediately fact
is
a media play. I
work by understanding what you write
or I get your partnership our house.
Up.
Raise and I'm sure your partnership
or at the Jets doing is amazing OK or
else you can accept my resignation
effective immediately what is it
a job i guess i never mind I'm psyching
here the papers and Sunday games
Consolidated I want to drive over to
consolidated and see their accountants all K.
. Just got an OK.
OK.
And. The judge do
a little there's something I
want to say to you right now
there's a judge do
a little I've been working in this office.
All right you just want to see showdown
I guess. Yesterday you've been doing pretty
good work lately Well thank you Judge
Campbell who dependable and loyal right
from the facts well I smiled and I saw the
judge but Nation These are extraordinary
times for all of us. Some
of our biggest clients are affected. They
all complain that they're practically
working for the government watching them
claim that will be all they can do to stay
in business till
a next election so they're cutting expenses
right and left where they're going to
feel it naturally we must do something
about action but naturally.
I don't want to cut down the passion out
of my staff if I can possibly help it it
wouldn't be constructive so the only way
out as I see it is to tighten our belts
and asking everyone to take a twenty
five percent cut I'm taking it
a substantial cut in my own
place not drawing income it's
a psychosis but it hits all of us and these
are days of cyclists I judge are now
but I have the signs reversed all put
our shoulder to the wheel if we are to
survive I asked the shoulder to the
whale. The only thing is that you
understand Mason and I have three
shared your cooperation like yours.
Along if your division has oh I don't know
how i organization or you know that little
piece of property up on Park Avenue Yes
well the price is right.
Thank
you you thank
.
Did you one doesn't just amaze. Flank you.
Why are mourning Johnny Good morning.
How do you think I feel fine what time
is just three o'clock four o'clock
five o'clock I know. Two o'clock
is now well if you know
what time it is why did you ask me what
time it is what difference does it make
what time it is anyway I feel.
Around
a little wrong wrong wrong wrong wrong
wrong wrong wrong wrong wrong wrong wrong
wrong. Wrong wrong wrong wrong wrong
wrong wrong wrong wrong work.
Feel better now the old. Are you
comfortable perfectly comfortable
are you sure you're comfortable Well
certainly I'm sure I'm comfortable because
you think you'd be more comfortable
if you took your shoes off.
Can I help you I can do very nicely
by myself thank you I feel fine.
What time best of my comfortable How do I
feel if I think I've committed some kind
of
a crime or something just like I was
on the wetness that I can do with
a man comes home looking for
a little peace and quiet and what happens
blab blab blab Why didn't you call me
back why didn't you come home for dinner
or a million questions just because
a man I ran into Judge
Doolittle says no you sign.
Johnny you fool what difference
does it make whether you've got
a right no conscience or anything you say
knowledge should go alone which was just
on the good chance. That it was nice
for credit to write I made to do it
and I have the leg was
a good ear can you tell me you
feel better on the. Job he's got
a look at the you know the minute to open
a. Chain I don't feel. I want
to say I do I feel fine.
The next time you let me get right if you
don't take me with you. I'm going to
deploy. To the get a
good lawyer and I've got
a good story it's not that. Old
. OLD OLD OLD
a loony. To me
a. Movie
Moon. Moon.
No you. Know now you want
time you gotta go to live.
In the jungle this don't have. Is
it's time that all the towns like
that where only you back and live
lives of the back of your neck.
Around this the missing. List
to make no use looking for
a job who said I was looking for
a job. No it is nice to go
crime and people the same
the the. You.
Know you must be the fifteenth woman I've
had working. Too good to be true with
your way to go. Best woman I
ever had simply because it.
Breaks my heart I have to tell you about
never your man honey I know I'm not sure
how I'd never let you go never if I should
study you in getting rid of me you just
give me all your budget is the
head there that's much better
make an awful mess of things that you oh
no you won't just step right in and do the
job it's a pretty good job too
a whole lot better than you can
get on the outside taken care of
a nice young man and a sweet little baby
and alone later the two little put in
a ski but that's because there's just no
long and don't have nothing to do she was
simple. Little is
a whole lot older than you. And
she. She learned one thing
never met the street stop you from
enjoying the watermelon. But if you've got
a lot of them you mustn't say that Miss
Mason you not sure I want to melon but you
can't just pop up on all of them
this is the I always say so. In
a mouthful responded piece with.
Blushes. Thank you that's
your. Prayers your
car has our telephone number
has new certainly has
a telephone book and what do you suppose
he has at least called up maybe he forgot
all about such. A mother
a man doesn't invite you to New Year's Eve
party and then just forgot about maybe
we should go join him at the party Jay and
I told you I don't know where the party
is he told me made his hair in his car
at nine o'clock almost eleven now
possibly also to announce is engaged want
to us do it. I don't like that perhaps
he thought it would be
a little up good to have you in jail and
it is engagement on Amada Hall could be
awkward so off I don't know at all what are
we going to sit here only me waiting to
hear from me let's call him
up. All the same it might
fail but. Why should it be awkward when.
Operator Oh I don't want this
connection operator I'm calling.
Mr Carter. To. Say no no no
well I said Carter's house he left two hours
ago forget him. A baby definitely has
the sniffles ALL babies have done if your
car is called from you to be ridiculous
matter of fact I caught my coat from the
baby you had the sniffles all day and when
I took it temperature that's when he got
your cold he said he didn't he had no
temperature it isn't anything
Johnny it's just the sniffles I
suppose I ought to stay in my room all day.
Mother That's so that you don't have to
do anything of the kind Heaven knows I
try to read my room and board by doing
everything I can to help you know Mother
please this is New Year's Eve It's just
like every other day as far as I'm concerned
you are both perfectly willing to go
off and leave me all alone to wait for
the New Year. Perhaps exhaust to have
a c. Oh no mother part of you keep
saying things like that. Which cause.
The right. Oh I want.
Three those cars
a lot in Melbourne they not and haven't
they all cooped up some chicken and where I
work they came in the wine.
Well how do you know.
How I sold everything we don't have to
go out at all we can stay right here and
celebrate we don't know why now
that good night we'll have
a grand feast all of these chicken. Come
on it's no use even to have fun you know
it'll be easy to gestured to be just as
well I go to bed. Maybe there are some left
over for me tomorrow I never did approve
of delicious much to fall in but I do miss
a cookie doesn't say much from
on an idea and takes tadpoles.
Times are different now when I was married
every well brought up to do something
about cooking. By Jane what is it I can't
cook I can't keep up I don't know how I'm
going to the bank yet I'm sure I don't know
what you're talking about if you do you
are going to be the first moment you saw
me you say to me because you want to join
me to marry you must do
a little good idea I never said anything
like that you handed out it enough though
I did nothing to salt but they engage my
mother I was never on gays to you as doing
them all well not perhaps Gage and even if
I had been you should keep talking about
it to Jane all the time I don't see why she
should be so touchy about touchy that's
why you hate me when you please know that
I go along she can say anything she likes
. I know my place I'm just
a guest and I'm welcome for cryin out loud
What's the matter with you nothing the
matter with me oh this is my house not
bother with you Jane I do anything I was
having you around me everything I say is
wrong and everything I know it's well
drained well you're just about to have
to mention the job and you just do
a little now stop it thanks all.
All right there you see
what you might meet
a mother we're said to me to know I guess
of course you're called Donna Bob and all
right if you will be what is wrong why
can't you get along with why can't you get
along with me because she hates me you
know how I don't think so nice between
taking care of
a baby in the house and cooking in the
dining I don't have that anymore. I can
spend only so many cities.
How do you.
Johnny. Where you going. I don't
know that I want to get away from
that right wait
a minute. Because
you want me to go with
you which understand
a man wants to be alone or want to work.
So I generally really saying you don't
have to apologize would you rather I
think I'm with you to the right you
know I don't like you go ahead and have
a good time. You can come along
if you want to share you know
my course you know why we have
a wonderful time we just we see. A
little Johnny what happened. I don't know.
Maybe I pulled
a dirty trick on you when I took the center
out of your I was. I mean. I mean every
. Single mistake was in. Our marriage.
To me I've gotten into that I've got
no place at the office I've made
a home school graduate if you just like
mother said. Jane just hasn't worked out
it's. Worked out we haven't
had any real trouble maybe
a few weeks only little things little
things or people have to make when they get
married. Maybe we should have
had the baby. All generally
have to worry about the baby I'm crazy about
him I'm crazy about you too Jane and I
drive really wanna. Got your
whole life her head of well.
No. Crank down time just
can't be great. I'm going to
hold you back under
contract. It was no come
to.
The point is that you call starting.
Your life. It was time I saw
something to celebrate. Now. We have.
Opinion.
For the day Jim.
Thanks.
A lot. An
L. N N.
A long way. Thought Oh thank you.
Thank you I thought I. Think
I'll go swimming with the baby and happy.
Thanks
a. Number one
else yes thank you
Sarah I had was
a mess up in your. Own
Carolina angina happy
doing what you just said. Want
to say to your father and then I
got it I have it and I have to own
one last thing the stone alone.
And by having
a can of the goods to babies. The
baby bump to the man with the baby.
The baby with. Something
you want to call your new.
Doctor healer. Come into the office and.
I don't know about.
You going to get your wife the doctors it's
bad news I don't want her to go but she
has good staff. You tell
me Dr your baby has taken
a new look of hers with the script because
of some cases and I'm sorry to say that
the congestion is increasing. Now this is
here and you want it worked out in some
cases without it we don't stand a
chance with it well perhaps we have
a ghost of the chance. We must get some
of that here was who is first every hour
counts I don't know whether we can locate
in the other day in the city or not I'm
going to check up on the family. Doctor
please don't tell my wife I will.
Get into the city health department and I
have nine Germans and just out make one
hundred five Johns Hopkins and bottom
are dying and shipped all we had to the
epidemic in Mexico yes the epidemic on
a pole here in Salt Lake we can spell you
six hundred fifty miles but how are you
going to get a lot of here in
a storm. Like
I see just
a little I don't think that this hour
of the morning got to wake him up why I
couldn't do that I just got to he knows me
I work for I've got to say I'm sorry but
Judge Douglas we would never allow me to
break this to you but I don't know when
you might do that what are you going
you must do this is Tell Rachel.
Judge him
a little just so I. Could
I wake up bike up so
I'm sorry to wake you up like what is it
I've got to talk to you right now are you
drunk Mike yet my heart really got pneumonia
you must be drunk waking me up in the
middle of the night like this is
outrageous I never heard of such
a thing next minute this is your idea of
what I knew you know you listen to me Now
you listen to me when you ask me to cut
down on the obs I talk and I don't believe
about it but I shut up because that the
reason the baby had to sleep on the back.
Well what if what you're talking about my
baby's in the hospital dying on the Mon
you dying dying I can understand
yes yes my baby you know baby
why didn't you get in touch with you before
trying to talk to me. Or. I don't need
sympathy I need serum there is money in New
York there's none anywhere around here
let's finally found someone solid like
setting and it's two thousand miles away and
every hour counts because the calm I can't
because I can't because of the leg up at
Cerro and the only way to get to the other
supply five mothers terrific storms over
Europe all the planes are grounded if
there's just one thing that we could do now
mission you must get hold of yourself I
know just how you feel but you must get
hold of yourself suppose the plane's on the
ground they could put it on one of the
fastest trains can do knowing that kept
a cold every hour counts
every minute counts we need
a plane from Salt Lake City but we have
a plan and. The pilot wants five thousand
dollars to fly out of to New York
or not allowed so I'd like to have
a body else to turn time on well what do
you spend it on my check book get my check
and get the
a pen with one of the right and find out
where the new one is telling off the ship
so it would. Have gotten in touch with
the soon I'm going to learn about that
sooner we'll have it here
and in plenty of time to.
Oz. The.
Gas most amazing the service here on the
money here too and I could certainly use
that kind of help but the weather got so
bad it's impossible to take off that's all
. What can I do. I
know exactly how you feel I'm
a married man myself I got
a couple of kids I'm going
to think of them. Why why
a bold letter she says if I do go she
won't be here when I get back I get back
what we're going to do with
a guy like this let me talk now listen you
know what do you think they say that so
if I plan you can expect anybody in
his right mind to fly a plane on
a night like this especially in
OK with whiskers I don't see it.
Sure
a step which certainly like to help you
out and then no other place you could get
some of the staff. Well maybe in
a few hours when the
weather clears up. Now
wait a minute but
a take it easy suppose
we well maybe I just
want to take no for an answer all the wire
that I buy your plane you don't know how
it is you've got kids your own suppose you
were in his place why can't you take my
plan and I'm going to insurance
I couldn't get them all in
a minute keep your shirt on I'll give you
half the money if you allow me the great
what if you're correct that you can keep
the whole five I don't need. I think
you're crazy of us all right
if you want to of all K.
Body relax.
You know we cannot. Know
how to do not move.
With.
Cancer like they're going to go. To
me like I'm going to be in five.
Years all right he's holding his own there
they're going to see I don't if you're
that that's just my doctor why don't you
want me to know please don't worry I don't
know why don't you want
me on the. Whole. I.
Landed. The i'm the rocks
on the Oxygen don't let it
open to the fear you. Know I want you to
lie down and rest I'll give you something
to make you sleep with you this is the
other side of the break the ice we.
Start. When couldn't sleep
in the little life.
Baby dies I wanted and I know
I've noticed. That John the.
Baby to you on the one you.
Were coming. To is the
same. In essence if you met him
you come to know me as an actress
you have just. Do you know when you're
reading those when you have no one to say.
That after the loss. Of the
real loving and I was told was
a bit of over at last Well the sister that
used most domestic problems in six weeks
and said that as
a basis Oh but it does
exist. Because this.
Book was. The Along comes.
A real
nail in
the bail.
Ileal the in the
a long way. To
the rear.
And.
The IT.
Air. And the common
commercial entity twenty four
command Conway. The man. Can't you read me
Conway. Can't you read me. Imam Conway.
Chemical I know of to read meaningless still
can't contact Conway Starman creeping
over the rocky land. And out of the
marshes it all stations stand by to
contact Conway just wipe the back
a colleague how do I The marshal and the
twenty four The replace twenty four is
normal you have we can wait for the Dago
poet my twenty one it was like in your it
me joint to come with. A A.
Lowly home not we haven't
seen or heard a plane on
a. Farm with
a warrior Senate version
parted out with pleasure Mary.
To. It.
You come.
I'm not
a cat. At the. Well
how much the Chilean. People we had
a little. Good cling.
To want to see him go off
and. Release help under the.
Small helpless he can't do anything for
himself he can't do to do anything for
him.
REM and.
Thank.
You.
And I.
As.
July or another think about this
is this year was a year long
a couple of hours. We're
. Not.
Always be together. Just like this.
Were you when you heard
the you know mercifully
a lot of what is happening
Never mind that.
But places is never any corners where day
three hundred miles an hour you walk.
For much Central High.
St Francis Hospital New York City. RUSH.
Alone. On operators I want. To St
Francis Hospital in New York
City. In the first in charge.
Eighty eight.
Hours.
A day.
Old. Age.
Hoping. That this is. The back
of the song.
Well gentlemen I guess four is about
enough on a business day I saw
a very good job but ended
a bad time you bought one
I sent Conway calling
Doolittle and there are certain things
gentlemen that I want distinctly understood
now I call this meeting of all the partners
in order to make my position clear once
and for all that before I accept your offer
of partnership in the firm of Doolittle
measures met doing
a little posh and Carter you must know that
I consider the methods of this farm of
the present time over five young
self-satisfied high handed and far away in
a fashion he's famous to me that
I have and I demanded by the
change effective immediately. I
mean Scuse me I hope we have disrupted
anything important Johnny I know you guys do
a little mind we just couldn't wait to
get the best out of what happened what
happened what happened the
baby can talk. Oh they
don't believe us come on darling let's
prove it to them show the now don't be
afraid speak up say did he say Daddy come
on darling say Daddy come woman say Daddy
just because I don't be afraid
to go and say Daddy daddy
daddy daddy daddy said Daddy
can one Johnny say Daddy
say that's not why.
You.